Hey, if you're watching this, you work in sales and you've been tasked with building a total adjustable market based on your ideal customer profile
Let's just start with this premise. You are selling observability tooling for
VPs of engineering and it's a plus if they sell dating compute because there's kind of like an intuition of like these guys probably care about
observability right and let's say, you know
You've been in this game for a while and you're you recognize like hey like this is the general, you know
kind of best practice workflow in order to you know, enrich leads with like verified contacts and then
Send outbound email campaigns as a result
Let's say you've been a veteran in this space you already have an intuition for the provider sprawl that's at play
And so we've even heard this anecdotally where you know, someone is extracting data from Apollo and crust data
To build like some, you know general heuristics on the companies that they're looking for flooded into clay for enrichment
So they have some like basic observability
But even then there's a lot of like CSV, you know
Shepherding shepherding that you know
It doesn't really feel like conducive for the time to value that's required for that, right?
And so I'm actually going to belabor this point here like just step by step
So let's say you're starting from scratch. It kind of looks like this where one
You are swapping your credit card or signing enterprise contracts with a bunch of providers over here
And it's even extra painful
If it's your first time navigating, you know
A lot of you know, the vendors and the UI and the UX kind of learning curve that comes with it, right?
Let's say you get used to that. Step two is you still have to haphazardly shuffle CSV's between these providers
And even then you're only getting like 60% 7% of like even you know, the coverage that you want, right?
From there, let's say you're generally okay with that and you say hey
I want to you know paste in some CSV's into
Cloud code so that it can churn through and like run some lead scores, but it's not really based on a saving procedure
So you just kind of go like oh, I think cloud code has a general common sense. So good luck, right?
We just can be a little bit, you know anxiety inducing from there
Let's say we're even okay with that then we go into, you know waterfall enrichment, you know
Going and funneling that CSV through a prospect on lead magic. You could even use like MCP's but even then you know
There's no real like cost visibility. It's just kind of like brute forcing its way until it gets a positive result, right?
Let's say we're even okay with that
The next step is to shuffle that CSV back into cloud code in order to personalize a copy maybe throw in a reddit thread
So there's like this like engineering colloquial speak
so it really sounds like really empathetic to this audience that we want to reach out to and
then from there you got a wrangle that to finally export a final CSV or
Connected to MCP's or API's through things like Salesforce and instantly in order to actually, you know, make that campaign happen
Right and even if you're technical, right?
There's a lot of brittle glue code in between that can still make this a really cumbersome process
And if anyone taps your shoulder to go like hey
You know, how exactly did you come to this process or can we tweak something?
It feels like you're you know
I have to tear down that house of cards and rebuild from scratch
Right and so there's actually a better way to do this without feeling like this toil has to be
You know the norm for you and that's through deep line or essentially you just enter a prompt and we provide all
These integrations out of the box because deep line is signed contracts, you know
I have the wholesale level with all of them, right and everything's in this very kind of transparent
auditable kind of step-by-step way in order to go from starting from simple prompt all the way to
Export CSV or actually just launch the campaign directly, but seeing is believing. So let's just get into it
I'm gonna run this and then essentially it's going to spin up a local host in my browser
And then you're gonna see something that looks and feels like this
And she's amped just like that. You'll notice over here
It shows a step-by-step exactly what it's gonna do without me having to go into like very kind of handholdy detail of hey deep line
I want you to behave in this exact way
Hey, great now deep line is asking me to prove running a full kind of paid run on the waterfall process
And so let's just do that
Okay, she's amped just like that it's done but let's say hey
I actually want to reason through this to make sure it did everything that I expected to do, you know, step one
Looking at some of these basic outputs one is deep line with cloud code took time to look across data and store some companies that meet
Our criteria of working and data or compute infrastructure. Great. That looks good going back it
Did a basic pilot to look at some names and enrich a couple of handful of emails just to make sure we're on the right track
Before we approve a full run. Okay, that looks good as well
So let's go back over here and then over here
this is where it enriched the leads and you can literally see how the waterfall works and how
At the certain point in the waterfall that the email source was verified from a specific source
Whether it was natively or through Prospeo or you could even add lead magic in the mix
from there
Let's go back and then ultimately we get to the final
CSV output with all the hundred leads
With all the information such as the scoring
The email body personalization hook every little thing under the Sun
So I feel really confident it's doing what I wanted to do and you can only imagine just based off the illustration
I provided earlier all the toil all the little nitpicky things that feel like death by a thousand paper cuts in
Order to get a structured result like this can feel pretty overwhelming and all of that just kind of happens automatically with course
Correction along the way just because clock could a deep line work really well together
And so yeah, basically in summation
You don't have to live in a world
Where playing CSV Sherpa is your toil as some normal you get to work with?
Tooling that understands what best practice looks and feels like in addition to having a methodology for lead scoring
and it's as simple as having cloud code on your terminal and then also having
Deepline downloaded simply by copying and pasting this link and moving on with your life. Have fun, y'all