Hey, if you're watching this, you work in sales as either a growth engineer, a GTM engineer,
and you're trying to build an email campaign based off some, you know, trends and product
analytics that you've been noticing that's stored within Snowflake.
But you realize that there's, you know, a couple problems here.
One is things are not, you know, quite synced between this and my CRM.
In this case, it's Adio.
It could be Salesforce in your case.
And then also my campaign tool called Instantly.
And I think to myself, like, yeah, you know, for maybe 20 users, I can just like shuffle
some CSVs around and like eyeball data quality and move on with my life.
But let's say I have a million plus users.
That's not going to be very kind of repeatable and realistic and very error prone.
And I don't want to do a bunch of like Excel V look-a-backer bets either.
And also if I use like Claude plus like MCP, it doesn't necessarily have the guardrails
and permission scopings, you know, that I want.
And so what would it look like to make that feel really easy and smooth, you know, in
deep line?
Well, let me just show you, you know, I'm just going to copy and paste a prompt that
already exists over here.
And essentially what I want to do with this fictional kind of problem scenario is this.
One, I have a bunch of power users that are using a tool called Pulse and I want them
to get to use our new AI tool that we're trying to sell them called Spark.
And so what I want them to do is, hey, I want you to look at this cohort analytics table
within Snowflake.
And then I want you to sync that and create attributes within Adio.
And then based off that, I want you to create an email campaign and instantly and then
offer them 100 and free credits to incentivize them to try it out.
And then they just, you know, have a natural momentum from there.
You notice over here, it just launched what's it called a local process so that we can track
the work along the way, right?
From that plain English prompt is able to see, hey, I'm going to do all these things,
inspect Snowflake, you know, pilot Adio, create the instantly campaign, move on with our lives,
right?
And then it's running.
I want to show you like, hey, how exactly does DeepLine, you know, integrate safely
and clearly with all these different things?
If it's not, you know, basic MCP, well, they built their own, you know, API integrations.
Step one, let's just go with Adio.
Over here, let's say I want to, you know, there's managed sync, but let's say I want
to reconnect because I'm connecting for the first time.
It's going to look and feel something like this, where it's going to say, hey, these
are all the permissions that's going to give you, we're going to give you a quick warning
given that, you know, it's an early stage product and move on with there.
For now, I'm going to cancel because, you know, I don't need to reconnect anything.
Now let me show you Snowflake, where assuming I already have a user scope to DeepLine with
some like basic Snowflake SQL commands, all I have to do is copy and paste, you know,
some basic information.
This is like account identifier, you know, the warehouse and the database, etc., right?
And then lastly is the instantly API key.
And all I have to do is just copy and paste API key source from instantly and just move
on with my life.
And that's it, right?
No kind of belabored rituals and MCP acrobatics, just hey, like tried and true robust API integrations
and move on with their lives, okay?
And now let's go back to how DeepLine is running right now.
Okay.
So it was over here.
DeepLine prompted me to, you know, ask some clarifying questions, which is totally great.
And so over here, yep, all six recommended.
Yep, I'm going to draft.
I don't want to activate immediately for the campaign.
Which variant?
Yeah, let's do this.
Yep, let's do that.
Submit those answers and then have DeepLine keep trucking along.
All right, cool, then it prompted me again.
Let's do it.
Now it's all done.
Let's gut check.
Hey, did this do all the things I wanted to do?
Let's start from the end and go backwards.
We're going to go to instantly.
Let's refresh this page.
Do I see a campaign?
Ooh, what do I see here?
I'm going to see leads, yep, it looks like these, it looks like I got six leads.
Okay, I'll double check that later.
Got sequences and bam, I got some email copying.
That looks what I expect it to look like.
And then now I'm going to mess off, hey, did the instantly source the data correctly?
You know, let's go over here and then even gut check, hey, you know, pulse power, no
spark is one of the users, you know, that's what row six.
Just like this guy over here and then let's actually add an attribute over here.
You'll notice, hey, we have some net new columns that we can add to this.
And so I'm going to go here, I'm going to add life cycle segment and bam, just like
that.
I got one, two, three, four, five, six and yeah, just like that.
I didn't have to think through the idiosyncrasies and nuances of, hey, how do I properly connect
to snowflake, to adio and to instantly with all the permission scoping without having
to configure MCPs or learn the APIs because deep line abstracted all that for me.
And so in summation, this is a speed run to integrating all your GTM tools with deep line
with the cloud code and moving on with your life because you're bragging rights isn't
about, hey, how cool my stitch together code is.
Your bragging rights are, hey, I was able to create a repeatable, auditable system that
just works.
Have fun, y'all.
Bye.