Hey, if you're watching this, you work in sales
and you're trying to reach out to people.
And in order to reach out to those people,
you have to verify some emails along the way.
And there's one of three entry points that you can do this.
One is you can work on hopes and prayers
by prompting Claude Raw.
And then you get into some like immediate privacy
kind of blockers.
And then it just guides you to go,
hey, you know, connect an MCP through like Apollo,
zoom info, et cetera, move on with your life.
Or you're like, fine, let's do that.
You swipe a credit card with Apollo
or sign an enterprise contract.
And then you prompt it with an MCP.
And you think, hey, this looks like it's
doing what I want it to do.
But it only gets you 65% coverage.
And then you're like, oh, dang, I have to now do it the hard way.
Or essentially, I have to go through all these different
vendors, swipe a bunch of credit cards.
And then even with that, I still have
to shepherd this kind of CSV along the way,
even with Claude, to make sure it's doing what I want it to do.
And this can be a very error-prone process.
In addition to that, you don't have an intuition of like,
hey, is this going to cost me $10 to enrich these contacts,
or $20 or $50?
Who knows, right?
That's where you don't have to kind of live
with these kind of locked-in pads of toil,
where there's a better way with Deepline, where it abstracts
a lot of the best practices and just bakes them in natively.
And so this is what it can look like, the Deepline way.
Specifically, you get to run from a single prompt
and Claude code with this simple skill
once you've already downloaded Deepline.
And the key thing is this.
You don't even have to sign up personally
for all your separate enrichment providers.
We already have wholesale contracts with them,
so you get the price performance that you expect.
And we have a standard procedure to find the cheapest path
to a valid result for all the emails that you want to,
or all the contacts, I should say, you want to enrich.
And we just give you a very predictable roadmap of like,
hey, this is exactly how it's going to play out,
in order to get you the CSV that you expect.
But you know what?
Seeing is believing, and so let's just run it right now.
And so I'm going to do this with Claude code already
up and running, and then I'm going
to run this prompt right here.
OK, and you'll notice here that after I prompt Deepline
and it's ready to do its job, it launches a new tab
in my browser in order to go through the steps
I expect to see.
It's going to discover new companies to find CTOs from,
from Crustata, one of the providers that is just best
practice baked in, find the CTOs at each of those companies
based off that provider, and then waterfall
through that process.
And a little bit later, when it gets to this step over here,
I'll show you exactly, just very visually,
how that looks and feels.
Over here, you'll notice it asked me
for approval, which is really great.
So I know I'm going to spend around like $35
before I approve the full run.
Let's say, hey, that's good enough for me.
Let's make it happen.
Now you're thinking to yourself, like, hey,
what does the actual enrichment look and feel like?
Well, it looks something like this,
where every step of the way, it would
go through this preview of like lead magic, and find email,
and Prospeo.
And it found out like, hey, we were able to verify right away
this person's email just by checking up lead magic,
and we move on with our lives.
And we found eight, or I think it was like verified
off the top of my head, or like what, 10 of these?
And we figured out like, hey, that's
enough to deliver the five net new rows.
Let's move on from there.
And now you're probably thinking like, hey,
what does the actual output look like at the end of the day?
It looks something like this, where bam,
I get the company name, domain, the CTO,
and the verified email.
And we have to move on with our lives.
And so again, in summary, you don't
have to live through these kind of toils and entry points.
There's a much better default way
to work without all the cumbersome kind of grind
it takes to stitch everything together,
because DeepBlind already handles that for you.
Have fun, y'all.
Bye.